I will share with you in French my passion, aeronautics.
Я поделюсь с вами по-французски своей страстью, аэронавтикой.
All of this starts with an overly bland anecdote that happened to me a few years ago.
Всё это начинается с слишком слезливого анекдота, который произошел со мной несколько лет назад.
When a friend contacted me, being passionate about viations and ebident in Toulouse,
Когда мой друг связался со мной, увлекаясь прозвищами и еврейкой в Тулузе,
He had found pieces of aircraft in the land south of Toulouse and led to his identification.
Он обнаружил части самолёта на земле к югу от Тулузы и провел опознание.
I put photos of these pieces on a specialized website, quickly the answers arrived.
Я поместил фотографии этих статей на специализированный сайт, быстро пришли ответы.
These are parts of an English plane and other answers followed.
Это части английского самолета и другие ответы.
It was an April in caster, an English four-engine bomber, who in 1944 was beaten south of Toulouse.
Это был апрель в кастере, английский четырехмоторный бомбардировщик, который в 1944 году был избит к югу от Тулузы.
The person I was in contact with puts me in contact with a retired woman, Arlette,
Человек, с которым я общался, связывает меня с пенсионеркой, Арлетт,
who knew the story of this plane very well.
который хорошо знал историю этого самолета.
Arlette told me that she had taken care of welcoming the families of the crew members of this English plane,
Арлетт сказала мне, что она позаботилась о том, чтобы приветствовать семьи членов экипажа этого английского самолета,